I remember one time this dude called himself trying to date me or whatever.
I was looking for some like old pictures the other day and I had seen one of his texts where he had canceled on me because he said that he was hungover and was just going to stay home and watch movies with his mom.
There were so many things wrong with that.
And for the record, no, I did not ever see or try to see this person again.
Okay, but I did run into them at the Grove and they were with a white girl.
Oh, that's probably who he was lying to me about.
He was with a white girl.
He found time to take her out.
I also just wanted to add this last little tidbit.
He hit me up a couple of years later, as they always do.
Just like a little temp check, you know, and he texted me and then he said like, what's up?
And I had him back and said, yes.
And he was like, wow, I kind of didn't expect you to have the same number.
I say, yeah, I have the same number, but I'm not in the same tax bracket.
Yeah.
I'm not in the same tax bracket.